export const flashcardContent = [
    {
      question: "Name the types of financial statements",
      answer: "Balance Sheet, Income Statement, Statement of Stockholders' Equity, Statement of Cash Flows, Financial Statement Linkages"
    },{
      question: "What is accounting?",
      answer: "The process of recording, summarizing and analyzing financial transactions."
    }, {
      question: "What is the act of providing financial information to external users called?",
      answer: "Disclosure"
    }, {
      question: "What are assets?",
      answer: "Resources that provide future benefit to the company."
    }, {
      question: "What are financial activities?",
      answer: "Methods companies use to fund those investments. Financial management is the planning of resource needs, including the proper mix of financing sources."
    }, {
      question: "What are liabilities?",
      answer: "Obligations the company must repay in the future"
    }, {
      question: "What is the accounting equation?",
      answer: "Assets = Liabilities + Equity"
    }, {
      question: "What are operating activities?",
      answer: "The production, promotion, and selling of a company’s products and services."
    }, {
      question: "What is the formula for net income?",
      answer: "Net Income = Revenues -  Expenses"
    }, {
      question: "What is revenue?",
      answer: "Revenue is the increase in equity resulting from the sale of goods and services to customers."
    }, {
      question: "What is expenses?",
      answer: "The costs incurred to generate revenue, including the cost of the goods and services sold to customers as well as the cost of carrying out other business activities."
    }, {
      question: "What is a balance sheet?",
      answer: "A balance sheet lists the company’s investments and sources of financing at a point in time using the accounting equation."
    }, {
      question: "What is an income statement?",
      answer: "The income statement reports the results of a company’s operating activities over a period of time."
    }, {
      question: "What is the statement of stockholders’ equity?",
      answer: "The statement of stockholders’ equity, or simply statement of equity, reports the changes in the equity accounts over a period of time."
    }, {
      question: "What three categories are included on the statement of shareholders' equity?",
      answer: "Contributed capital, retained earnings, other stockholders' equity."
    }, {
      question: "What is retained earnings?",
      answer: "Retained earnings (also called earned capital) represents the income the company has earned since its inception, minus the dividends it has paid out to shareholders."
    }, {
      question: "What is a statement of cash flows?",
      answer: "The statement of cash flows reports net cash flows from operating, investing, and financing activi-ties over a period of time. "
    }, {
      question: "What is GAAP?",
      answer: "U.S. accountants have developed a set of standards and procedures called generally accepted accounting principles (GAAP). GAAP is not a set of immutable laws. Instead, it is a set of standards and accepted prac-tices, based on underlying principles, that are designed to guide the preparation of the financial statements. "
    }, {
      question: "What is FASB?",
      answer: "FASB is the seven member Financial Accounting Standards Board primary responsibile for setting financial accounting standards in the United States. It has published over 160 accounting statements governing the preparation of financial reports. These, along with numerous bulletins, interpretations, opinions, and earlier standards form the body of GAAP."
    }, {
      question: "What is profitability analysis?",
      answer: "Profitability analysis reveals whether or not a company is able to bring its product or service to the market in an efficient manner, and whether the market values that product or service. Companies that are consistently unprofitable are unlikely to succeed in the long run."
    }, {
      question: "What is the formula for the debt-to-equity ratio?",
      answer: "debt-to-equity ratio = total liabilities / total stockholders' equity"
    }, {
      question: "What two characteristics must be met for an asset to be reported on the balance sheet?",
      answer: "1. It must be owned or controlled by the company. 2. It must possess probable future benefits that can be measured in monetary units."
    }, {
      question: "What three characteristics must be met for liabilities to be reported on the balance sheet?",
      answer: "1. The future sacrifice is probable. 2. The amount of the obligation is known or can be reasonably estimated. 3. The transaction or event that caused the obligation has occurred."
    }, {
      question: "What is an executory contract?",
      answer: "A contract where a future sacrifice of a known value is probably but the transaction has not occurred."
    }, {
      question: "What are examples of current liabilities?",
      answer: "Accounts payable, accrued liabilities, short-term borrowing, unearned revenues, current maturities of long-term debt"
    }, {
      question: "What are examples of non-current liabilities?",
      answer: "Long term debt, other long term liabilities"
    }, {
      question: "What is accounts payable?",
      answer: "amounts owed to suppliers for goods and services purchased on credit. Walgreens uses another common name for this account—trade accounts payable"
    }, {
      question: "What is long term debt?",
      answer: "Any portion of long-term debt that is due within one year is reclassified as a current liability called current maturities of long-term debt."
    }, {
      question: "What are types of stockholders'equity?",
      answer: "Common stock, additional paid-in capital, treasury stock, retained earnings, Accumulated other comprehensive income or loss"
    }, {
      question: "When should revenue be recorded?",
      answer: ", in an amount that reflects how much the company expects to be entitled from the transfer—even if there is not an immediate increase in cash."
    }, {
      question: "What is accrual accounting?",
      answer: "The practice of recognizing revenues when earned through the company’s operations and recognizing expenses as the assets used and obli-gations incurred in carrying out those operations."
    }, {
      question: "What is cost of goods sold?",
      answer: "COGS represents the cost of products that are delivered to customers during the period. The difference between revenues (at selling prices) and cost of goods sold (at purchase price or manufacturing cost) is called gross profit."
    }, {
      question: "What is a t-account?",
      answer: "Accountants commonly use a graphic representation of an account called a T-account, so named because it looks like a large T. One side of the T-account is used to record increases to the account and the other side is used to record decreases."
    }, {
      question: "The ________ side of a T-account represents debits.",
      answer: "Left"
    }, {
      question: "The ________ side of a T-account represents credits.",
      answer: "Right"
    }, {
      question: "What is a journal entry?",
      answer: "A journal entry is an ac-counting entry in the financial records (journals) of a company. The journal entry is the bookkeeping aspect of accounting. "
    }, {
      question: "What are the steps of the accounting cycle?",
      answer: " Analyze > Record > Adjust > Report > Close"
    }
];
